ALEX PERRY

INCIDENT MANAGER

PERSONAL PROFILE

I have worked in Telecommunications since 2006 and have developed a high degree of Customer Service and Technical skills across multiple roles and business areas, Providing services in fields such as Technical Support, Customer Service, Service Delivery and Major Incident Management

CONTACT INFORMATION

+61 433 671 631 +351 920 047 732 alexander.h.perry@gmail.com Sydney, Australia Lisbon, Portugal

www.linkedin.com/in/alexander-h-perry

SKILLS AND ABILITIES

- Native English
- Basic Portuguese
- Strong Written and Verbal communication Skills
- Customer Service Experience
- High level of problem solving and analytical skill
- Advanced Excel, including spreadsheets, analytics, Macros and VBA
- Experience in Software Development Languages: VB, C#, AutoIT, PHP, JavaScript, HTML, CSS

EDUCATION

SWC Training - 2007Certificate III Customer Contact ICT30102

Tyndale Christian School - 2004 Higher School Certificate

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Incident Manager

Singtel Optus Pty Ltd | Jul 2020 - present

- Containing and representing Business customers internally for high-severity network and single-service incidents within the Optus Complex Fixed network.
- Reporting, Trending, analysis and support in triaging, resolving and Reviewing a subset of high-priority incidents

Order Delivery Specialist

Singtel Optus Pty Ltd | Aug 2016 - Jul 2020

- Compliance, Quality Control and Provisioning of Optus Complex Business products.
- Reporting and analysis of order volumes and processing times.

Technical Support Consultant

Singtel Optus Pty Ltd | Oct 2007 - Aug 2016

- Customer Service and Technical Support for Optus consumer services and Products
- Reporting and Analysis of call statistics, KPIs and performance management.
- Senior Agent Support, Quality Analysis and Coaching

IT Consultant

Dominos Pizza Conder | Nov 2010

- Upgrade and Calibration of POS, Server and Network systems
- Fault Troubleshooting and Readiness Testing

Customer Service Representative

Teletech Holdings International | Nov 2006 - Oct 2007

- Customer Service and Technical Support for Telstra Bigpond
- Performance management, Quality Assurance and Coaching

Junior Web Designer

W3B Design | 2002-2003

- Website Design and Maintenance
- Graphics Design

Assistant Manager

Dominos Pizza Australia | Feb 2001 - Nov 2006

- Customer Service, Food Preparation, Handling and Delivery
- Staff recruitment, training and rostering
- Complaint management